https://www.z90.com/privacy-policy/

ON AIR EVENTS CONTESTS MORTON IN THE MORNING LISTEN LIVE
HomeListen LiveOn AirMorton in the MorningEdinaD-RockPandarMatt MonyRomeoWillPJSunday Night Slow JamsFeaturesLean on ZPhone JibbaHeads UpBlogsMusicPlaylistNew MusicTrending 20 with PandarEventsZ90 EventsConcerts and ShowsSubaru presents Concerts in your CarConcert Pre-SaleAround TownBuy Local: Support & Share Local BusinessesRide With Emilio – Join our TeamSubaru presents Movies in your CarSan Diego Coronavirus UpdatesPhoto + VideoPhotosVideosContestsContactGet A Hold of UsNewslettersCareers at Z90.3DJ’s For HireContest Terms & ConditionsPrivacy PolicyLet's be Social
© 2020 Local Media San Diego. All Rights Reserved.
Privacy PolicyThis privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for z90.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. 2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. 3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. 4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:// See what data we have about you, if any. // Change/correct any data we have about you. // Have us delete any data we have about you. // Express any concern you have about our use of your data.Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (858) 888-7000 or via email.Cookies We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.Links This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.Surveys & Contests From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.Recent Posts FEEL GOOD FRIDAYS: Couple uses catering deposit from canceled wedding to feed 200 people on Thanksgiving Buy Local: Support San Diego Businesses Share the Love Holiday’s in Your Car PRESENTED by Subaru! Holidays in your Car – The Best Drive Thru Holiday Light ShowVideoshttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t-k12ZrGf1ELet’s be Social© 2020 LOCAL MEDIA SAN DIEGO. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.
